jobsplazza.com 2014-06-30

# Privacy Policy | Jobs Plazza

Other than any other aspects we are much more concerned about the privacy policy as it would make a major difference in the building a relationship between us and our visitors. So we are always in a ready to go mode when it comes to answer our visitor about the privacy policy and terms and conditions too. So, here are the rules for our privacy policy and make sure that you go through it before using this website.

## **Log Files and Cookies**

As in case of other sites,  **“**[ **Jobs**](http://jobsplazza.com/) **[Plazza](http://jobsplazza.com/)” **too uses the data contained in log files in terms of IP address, ISP, website browsers, entry/exit pages, number of page views etc. On the other hand, ** ** “jobsplazza.in” ** ** uses cookies to store information about the browsed information and traces the visits of users on the pages. Through the web beacons we do make our concern on which browser the users targets our site.

## **Access Control**

If you’re a registered user or subscriber to this website, it’s strongly recommended that you should keep your authorized information like IDs and Passwords in a secure manner. As this is an educational and job portal, you may need to provide your registration number or bank information also. All these things are private to you only and kindly don’t disclose it outside in order to get an uninterrupted service. We are providing assistance to recover your login info and if you are feeling like somebody is accessing your account from other external source without your permission, directly contact us. This is the best possible manner through which we can resolve our issues.

## **Confidentiality and Security**

To avail the full service you need to make an account with us and to create that you require providing all correct information related to you. We’re ensuring to you that all such personal information is worth full. If under any circumstances you’re providing wrong information, without any prior notifications your account will be simply suspended.

## **User Submission**

“jobsplazza.in” contains both static and dynamic services and sometime our server may ask you to provide or upload files. Make sure that those files are in their proper format (text, image, pdf, audio or video) and should contain related information only that is required for your working process with this website. We will simply discard all those stuff that are not related and go against the rules.

## **Legal Objections and Clash**

Like we mentioned in our “terms and condition”, under our intellectual property rights all the material that are displayed here are private to us. You can follow our procedure to make a claim if you observe that something present over here violates your copyright rules. As we are working and will be worked with a reciprocated perceptive, for any type of disputes that will take place out of all these terms and conditions we will work together to resolve it. We strongly suggest you to make contact with us before resorting to prosecution so that we will be able to seek a decision directly.

##
